<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string-array name="msgs_array">
        <item>Hey! Check out Randomology in the Play Store! It is awesome!</item>
        <item>Frankly, my dear, I don\'t give a damn.</item>
        <item>I\'m gonna make him an offer he can\'t refuse.</item>
        <item>Go ahead, make my day.</item>
        <item>May the Force be with you.</item>
        <item>Fasten your seatbelts. It\'s going to be a bumpy night.</item>
        <item>You talking to me?</item>
        <item>What we\'ve got here is failure to communicate.</item>
        <item>I love the smell of napalm in the morning.</item>
        <item>Love means never having to say you\'re sorry.</item>
        <item>The stuff that dreams are made of.</item>
        <item>E.T. phone home.</item>
        <item>Made it, Ma! Top of the world!</item>
        <item>I\'m as mad as hell, and I\'m not going to take this anymore!</item>
        <item>I think this is the beginning of a beautiful friendship.</item>
        <item>A census taker once tried to test me. I ate his liver with some fava beans and a nice Chianti.</item>
        <item>There\'s no place like home.</item>
        <item>I am big! It\'s the pictures that got small.</item>
        <item>Show me the money!</item>
        <item>Why don\'t you come up sometime and see me?</item>
        <item>I\'m walking here! I\'m walking here!</item>
        <item>You can\'t handle the truth!</item>
        <item>I want to be alone.</item>
        <item>After all, tomorrow is another day!</item>
        <item>Round up the usual suspects.</item>
        <item>I\'ll have what she\'s having.</item>
        <item>You know how to whistle, don\'t you, Steve? You just put your lips together and blow.</item>
        <item>You\'re gonna need a bigger boat.</item>
        <item>Badges? We ain\'t got no badges! We don\'t need no badges! I don\'t have to show you any stinking badges!</item>
        <item>I\'ll be back.</item>
        <item>Today, I consider myself the luckiest man on the face of the earth.</item>
        <item>If you build it, he will come.</item>
        <item>My mama always said life was like a box of chocolates. You never know what you\'re gonna get.</item>
        <item>We\'ll always have Paris.</item>
        <item>I see dead people.</item>
        <item>Well, nobody\'s perfect.</item>
        <item>It\'s alive! It\'s alive!</item>
        <item>Houston, we have a problem.</item>
        <item>You\'ve got to ask yourself one question: Do I feel lucky? Well, do ya, punk?</item>
        <item>You had me at "hello."</item>
        <item>One morning I shot an elephant in my pajamas. How he got in my pajamas, I don\'t know.</item>
        <item>La-dee-da, la-dee-da.</item>
        <item>Greed, for lack of a better word, is good.</item>
        <item>Keep your friends close, but your enemies closer.</item>
        <item>As God is my witness, I\'ll never be hungry again.</item>
        <item>Well, here\'s another nice mess you\'ve gotten me into!</item>
        <item>Say "hello" to my little friend!</item>
        <item>What a dump.</item>
        <item>Elementary, my dear Watson.</item>
        <item>Take your stinking paws off me, you damned dirty ape.</item>
        <item>Of all the gin joints in all the towns in all the world, she walks into mine.</item>
        <item>Here\'s Johnny!</item>
        <item>They\'re here!</item>
        <item>Is it safe?</item>
        <item>Wait a minute, wait a minute. You ain\'t heard nothin yet!</item>
        <item>No wire hangers, ever!</item>
        <item>I have always depended on the kindness of strangers.</item>
        <item>Hasta la vista, baby.</item>
        <item>Open the pod bay doors, please, HAL.</item>
        <item>Hello, gorgeous.</item>
        <item>Listen to them. Children of the night. What music they make.</item>
        <item>Oh, no, it wasn\'t the airplanes. It was Beauty killed the Beast.</item>
        <item>My precious.</item>
        <item>Listen to me, mister. You\'re my knight in shining armor. Don\'t you forget it. You\'re going to get back on that horse, and I\'m going to be right behind you, holding on tight, and away we\'re gonna go, go, go!</item>
        <item>A martini. Shaken, not stirred.</item>
        <item>Who\'s on first.</item>
        <item>Life is a banquet, and most poor suckers are starving to death!</item>
        <item>I feel the need - the need for speed!</item>
        <item>Carpe diem. Seize the day, boys. Make your lives extraordinary.</item>
        <item>Snap out of it!</item>
        <item>My mother thanks you. My father thanks you. My sister thanks you. And I thank you.</item>
        <item>I\'ll get you, my pretty, and your little dog, too!</item>
        <item>I\'m the king of the world!</item>
        <item>When Bruce Banner gets mad, he turns into the Hulk. When the Hulk gets mad, he turns into Chuck Norris.</item>
        <item>When Chuck Norris talks, everybody listens. And dies.</item>
        <item>Bill Gates thinks he\'s Chuck Norris. Chuck Norris actually laughed. Once.</item>
        <item>Chuck Norris ordered a Big Mac at Burger King, and got one.</item>
        <item>Chuck Norris sleeps with a pillow under his gun.</item>
    </string-array>
</resources>
